Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Good evening.
We've got our morning tea time.
I'm Shirichai Misturaku.
I'm sorry, I'm talking so fast.
I didn't hear you say it that early in the morning.
I'm surprised.
You were early.
You've been talking a lot with Mayu today.
That's true.
She's talking so fast because her "talk switch" is on.
I'm so surprised.
You're early in the morning.
That happens sometimes.
Thank you very much.
You were so fast!
I didn't catch the tempo just now!
You raised the BPM too much!
That's why
I will be your facilitator today.
Please do.
I'm talking too fast.
And I'm here with Mayu today.
I'm Mayu Marika, seat number 3.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you.
Let's begin.
The fun and fluffy showroom of Shrimps!
Yay!
Today is our 58th showroom.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
It's quite unusual to only have two people here.
I know you've been doing a lot of that intake lately.
Like a showroom with just the two of you.
That's for sure.
It was the same last time.
If it's just the two of them, it's going to be normal.
Hey.
I'll show you our private life together.
Is it going to be okay?
Almost.
It's really private.
Who was it last time?
Kaho.
It was Kaho, right?
No, it wasn't.
Yu no Ee...
Yu no Emanaka.
I wonder what they're talking about.
That's for sure. I'm super curious.
They're the two I'm worried about.
It's like they combined there.
In case you're wondering...
Ebichu's
The showroom that's so cute and fluffy
It's our little sister showroom.
Yuka's showroom is the sister showroom of Yuka's showroom.
Yes, you can!
There are many original avatars of EBITCHU's showroom
We have many original avatars
And the showroom too!
The ghost-san says that Yuuchi-chan is very solid.
"Yuuchan, you're doing great!" she says as she changes her clothes.
Wow, that's great!
I'm sure he'll talk without us.
He's probably talking without us.
Maybe she's easier to talk to than I thought.
We'd love to have you join us for a free or paid tee time.
If you tease us, we'll give you a chance to win.
You can get one if you tee it up.
If you don't have it yet, please try it on.
Please do!
Please!
I'm so angry.
This comment pisses me off.
They're both over 50 years old.
Oh, wow.
But you're over 50 all by yourself?
I don't know.
That pisses me off.
This is a big deal to everyone over the age of 25.
You're making an enemy of me.
I don't care.
Age is just a number.
It's a number of experiences.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can't believe you're worried about your age.
It's a small world we live in.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It says, "Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's our fault.
I'm 45 years old and I'm alone
You're so cute, Yuzuru!
You're the cutest
That's how I'm going to do it
I'm going to do it like this.
I'm thinking of doing a spread time here.I was thinking of doing a spread time here.
I'm going to make sure that a lot of people see this distribution.
I'll announce it on Twitter in my fingers.
So please retweet!
So, what should we do for the pose?
Yuzuru is saying something good, so let's go with Yuzuru.
Yuzuru
Yuzuru commented.
Yuzuru's inside is perfect.
Congratulations.
Shall I make a yuzuru comment?
I'm waiting for yuzuru.
What are you doing, posing for me?
Today you have the privilege of being a yuzuru.
He's 45 because he's cute.
I'm 48 too!
You're so cute!
Happy 20th birthday next month!
Yuzuru is very popular.
Anyone with the name Yuzuru
And New Yuzuru, too.
They're all nice people.
It's so random.
I turned 53 today.
Congratulations.
I'll pass this on to you.
Nice to give it to you.
I wonder if it was this one.
I think it was this one
This is Ai, right?
Cheese!
Here's another one!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Please spread the word!
Your hair is brighter than I thought it would be.
Like the lighting.
I'm surprised to see myself brighter than I usually see myself on this screen.
I'm surprised at how much brighter I look in this picture than I normally do.
You're right.
It's easy to lose hair color.
Maybe that's why.
I'm feeling it more and more.
I went for a treatment, so it's falling out a little bit.
I'm surprised at myself.
It's so beautiful.
I've said it over and over again.
But that's beside the point.
I'd like to get on with the project.
I can't wait to get started!
I can't wait!
I'm going to start today.
I'd like to do a project like this.
Let's call it
It's going to be fun and exciting!
Ankei Octopus Part
Yay!
Here it comes! Here it comes!
This is not just Ankei talk.
First of all
I'll tell you what "Ankei Talk" is.
Before the talk, we decide what we're going to talk about.
That's it.
I do it every time.
What a surprise!
We...
When Ayaka and I were out together...
Can't we do the showroom and the taco part?
We want to do the octopus part.
We were talking about it.
Thankfully and truly
It came true!
Yay!
Silver octopus
I have to do it the other way around.
Oh no!
Silver octopus.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Say you want to parse octopus.
"I want to eat octopus.
It's like they just let us eat takoyaki.
That's great!
In studio class.
You know, like cash?
Well, since you're here...
We should do a photo shoot with the takoyaki.
That's definitely the way to go.
It's the right thing to do.
That's right.
Takoyaki, right?
Takoyaki.
Let's do takoyaki.
It smells so good! I love takoyaki!
Yay!
We'll have shrimp-shaped takoyaki.
First of all, what flavor?
This is a normal takoyaki, with mayonnaise on the side because I don't like mayonnaise.Here is the normal takoyaki, served with mayonnaise, which I don't like, so it is served separately.
And here is the Negi-Dako.
I love it! We love this.
We have the same taste buds, so we usually like to eat the same thing.
The staff showed it to me and I said, "Oh! I said, "You've already picked it before, haven't you?
Yes, yes, yes. There was a new product, but we both said we liked it,
We both said we liked it, but it had a lot of sesame.
Sesame onion something.
I quit.
I'm an idol, you know.
I'm an idol, so I quit.
Normal is really delicious. After all, we've come full circle.
It's delicious after all.
I understand.
Everyone is talking about beer as a drink.
We are idols, right?
I think I'll have a Uron Tea and a Coke.
Yay!
Which one do you want?
Seriously, I didn't have any work until today, right?
No, I didn't.
It was just for the past hour. I just came here to eat takoyaki.
Mire-chan is the worst. She didn't even bring a script.
I didn't have a script, and I was wondering where it was, so I left it in the dressing room.
I was like a person who came to eat takoyaki.
Coke?
Cora! Thank you.
Bitter gin chile is good, you know?
I know.
I definitely used the wrong hand towel.
Here you go, hand towel.
It's only for this occasion.
This time only.
I'm glad. I'm glad I've been working in the showroom for so many years.
I'm glad.
I'm sorry about Yusumoto-san.
Yusumoto-san, by all means, please eat takoyaki in Osaka for my solo concert.
Please eat a lot of takoyaki. The real thing.
The real thing. It's delicious. Thank you very much.
Which one do you like better? I can't choose.
I don't know.
The fluffy Osaka style?
Or that crunchy silver takoyaki.
Ah...
I'm a little torn.
This one is a ray end.
Oh, I want mayonnaise. Thank you.
They both have their merits, don't they?
High-food? Yes, they're both good.
They both have their merits. So, you're either one or the other?
I don't know.
I was shocked the first time I ate takoyaki in Osaka.
I thought, "Is this the real takoyaki?
That's for sure. Until then,
You know, Gindako is the one,
I thought it was the right thing to do. That's right. I thought it was a takoyaki, but when I ate it for the first time, I thought, "Oh, this is so squishy,
When I ate it for the first time, I thought, "Oh, this is so squishy,
But it's so delicious. It's so good. And it has a salty flavor.
I love saltiness.
When I eat it, it tastes so good.
And the baked sweets, too, the soup stock is so good.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Well, well, I don't know which one to choose. I'm torn,
I'm torn.
Osaka?
Yeah.
This one's different,
You just had a cup of tea before the toast.
Why?
I was waiting for the toast.
Sorry.
Cheers!
Yay!
It's getting drier.
It's like this, when we're alone.
Let's start once we've eaten.
Which one do you want?
You can have either one.
Normal. I'll go with the green onion first.
Yay!
I like silver bulgur as silver bulgur.
I know, it's not a separate genre. It's not a kakuyaki. Gin-dako... good morning already.
Bon appétit!
Yum! Yum!
Good, pretty good, good, crunchy, good, good...
Great! The service is really nice and warm, because you bought it a while ago.
And everyone eats it right away because it's so hot, I know.
Thank you. Oh, and no more mugging.
Oh, we don't play Mogu-mogu rock-paper-scissors, so...
What? I thought you were supposed to eat takoyaki in one bite.
Not when they're really hot. But the people who are going out to buy takoyaki are practically eating takoyaki with us.
That's amazing. We don't get that often.
Gindako party!
Delicious.
I used to buy and eat silver cod roe all the time when I was in school.It's delicious. When I was a student, I used to buy and eat silver cod roe all the time.
I know. Me too.
When I was a little girl, I met a guy named Ei, and he had silver bullets underneath.
So it was always a silver bulgur.
Silver eggs or Misudo ramen.
Misudo is delicious.
It's just ramen with no ingredients.
It's delicious.
It's really good.
Thank you.
Thank you, Miyano.
It's good!
Yum!
I'm just eating so much. Are you guys eating, too?
Just in time.
It's so good!
They're having sushi at Silver Salad.
That's good.
That's good too.
The shiru soba is really good!
They have a noodle soup called "Sula Tang Men".
That's good too.
It's from Misudo, right?
I like Misudo's ramen noodles.
It says here that he eats Frugula in the morning because he has to work at night.
On the other hand, this morning?
This morning.
Morning.
I want some of that mekabo-okra beef bowl.
Wow!
Is there such a thing?
Gyudon with mekabo okra!
Likeya is good too!
But lately I prefer Yoshinoya.
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's true, isn't it?
I'll do the survey.
Shall I take it then?
Just in case.
Shall we?
It's more convenient this way.
The boss is angry with me.
I'm sorry, boss.
President Takahashi is angry with me.
I'm sorry.
Here's the questionnaire.
Yes, sir.
This way, please.
First of all, there are 7 questions.
You can vote for the number you'd like to hear.
We'll start with the most popular one.
Okay, okay, okay.
First of all...
Interim tour report
2. Family goods information
And 3, Hanaho Kobayashi's birthday party.
Though she's not here, happy birthday!
4Yasumoto Ayaka's birthday party
Happy Birthday to Ayaka Yasumoto!
5Something like that
6Such and Such a Place
Part 2
7Majigachi
Maji-Gachi-Free Talk
We did it last time, but this is a real free talk.
It's free talk for real!
Serious Free Talk
Free Talk for Real
This is a free talk session for 7 serious people!
We're just going to eat takoyaki again today.
Okay.
Please vote for your favorite.
Let's begin.
We'll eat takoyaki while you vote.
Eat, eat, eat.
Oh, it's so good!
It's really good.
I mean, it's delicious.
I'm getting nice and hungry.
Everything is getting out of hand here today.
But you know what, I had some soba before this.
I did it because I'm full.
I'm not full.
I've got just the right amount of appetite.
Come on.
Okay.
One.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Zero.
Here's the tally.
Let's see what we got.
Here we are.
Number seven.
Seven?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.Hey.
They prepared all this stuff for us.
Yeah.
Hey.
You know, you can listen to us anytime you want, really.
Really serious free talk.
It's serious.
I'm serious.
You know what?
I don't know if this is the best time to say this, but...
You're wearing a T-shirt today, right?
I'm wearing one too.
You can't see it.
You can't see it, but I'm wearing it.
You're wearing it.
I'm wearing it.
That's right.
And we'll wash your T-shirts and stuff, won't we?
Yes, I'll take it.
You know, for lessons and stuff.
Yes.
This is a little too close to a mid-tour report, but...
Let's collaborate!
At the Hiroshima concert...
I changed into my lesson clothes as usual.
And when I put on my lesson clothes, I thought... I thought...
I thought maybe it was just me.
So I thought I'd just do the lesson as usual.
Then it was time to get up, and Ikeuei-sensei, the P.E. teacher, was helping me with my ups.
You're really good, aren't you, Maya, at following the rules?
She's doing it!
Does that mean you're not from Hiroshima?
Oh! Ichikawa, Ichikawa.
It's in Ichikawa!
It's the Ichikawa show.
It looks like it.
But you're still curious? I thought...
I thought, "Doesn't this T-shirt stink? I said...
I was like... I know, right?
I've been thinking about it.
"It stinks, doesn't it?
What? That natto wasn't on the caterer's table today, was it?
But it smells like natto.
I said, "Yes, it smells like natto.
We were the only two sisters there at the time.
They all said yes.
I said I thought so too.
I hadn't mentioned it to anyone else who was there.
I just wondered if I was the only one.
Yeah, I was wondering if I was the only one who was having a bad day.
I thought maybe it was me.
Did I eat garlic like yesterday?
And then, as you said, it was raw and dry.
Yes, it was dry.
But they prepared it for me, so I can't complain about it.
What's more, when I asked him what was going on...
The washing machine in the room we rent for storage broke down.
So all the managers wrung it out by hand.
And that's what happened when they dried the clothes.
I thought, "How is that possible?
I'm sure there are 10 T-shirts
I want to give you 10 T-shirts, and the idea of hand wringing them out
It might be a nice story that makes you cry, but
but if you think about the time and effort, it's usually faster to take them to the laundromat.
It's faster to dehydrate them.
It's totally faster.
But you can't attack me.
There's no downside to this story.
But I was thinking...
How much of the smell can you take?
How much can I stand the smell?
The smell of fresh air is the hardest to endure
The smell of fresh air is the hardest to bear
Toughest.
What about everyone else?
I don't know about everyone else.
I'm like, "This is amazingly smelly.
It's amazing.
I wonder how much longer I can stand the smell.
It's true that fresh air is the worst smell in the world.
You know how they say it's the worst smell in the world?
That's what the numbers say.
There is a smell like a number, isn't there?
They say it's a strong number.
I have a sensitive nose, so it's relatively low.
That's right.
I always have rhinitis on a full stomach.
It's not that bad.
I can't wear perfume in the morning.
Is it too strong?
When I smell the perfume of the person next to me in the morning.
I can't stand the smell of my neighbor's perfume in the morning.
I can smell the drains.
I can smell it.
The river in Shibuya smells so bad.
I know
Shibuya river smell
Meguro river, right?It's the Meguro River, isn't it?
That's not the Meguro River.
Sewage sewage?
That's the waste water from the melting furnace.
It smells really bad.
The smell of ditch on a rainy day is really tough.
It really gets to you, doesn't it?
It makes me sick.
I don't mind the smell of the rainy season.
What do you mean by the smell of the rainy season?
You mean the smell of rain?
Then your nose must be on a high level.
My mom has a very sensitive nose.
That's why.
I can't smell her feet.
Isn't it bad?
People say, "Didn't you smell the neighbor's feet?
I don't know if I have rhinitis or what.
Like, "You should be careful.
They say, "They smell bad," but I don't know.
I don't know.
Well, that's pretty good.
It's really good for the nose.
Like the smell of a hotel refrigerator.
I don't even know what it smells like.
The smell of a hotel fridge.
There's two kinds of hotel fridges, right?
One smells like a machine and one smells like a machine.
There's the smell of machines.
And the smell of brand-new machines.
It smells like it's been here for a long time.
It's soaked in.
I'm pretty sure it's the guy from before.
I'd rather talk about the smell of octopus bread.
That's for sure.
I beg your pardon.
I apologize.
I was just wondering if this is how you eat takoyaki.
My appetite is a little low right now.
To be honest...
To be honest.
That's right.
Talking about eating takoyaki.
It's true.
But... my T-shirt really stinks.
We all put it on like this.
I thought I could breathe better when I smelled Sado.
But it's more than that.
The smell...
You can't cover up a bad smell with a good one.
It's a no-no.
But... I'm not saying who we are.
I'm not saying who, but we're amazing.
I know your sister.
I won't say who.
I'm not saying who.
We were in elementary school and middle school.
When we were teenagers.
When we were teenagers, we had a machine to work with.
A few times, this...
There was this one person that I met a lot of times at these machines that we worked with.
And her sister always smelled so good.
She smells so good.
She smelled so sweet and so good.
And I'm walking up to her and I'm like, "Smells so good, smells so good.
She doesn't like to take a bath.
He was wearing a lot of perfume like a foreigner.
He was just covering up the smell with a lot of perfume like a foreigner.
He only went out once a week.
Isn't that awful?
But it smells so good.
It smells so good.
But how can you get it to come out in a week when it usually does?
That's right.
This might go back to the previous showroom.
Aya doesn't really use perfume.
Maybe I'll just wash it off like Aya.
Ah...
Maybe she'll just let it flow.
Maybe she just flushes it down the drain.
Maybe she's French.
It's not that Aya doesn't like taking baths, it's just a beauty regimen.
That's true.
It's a beauty regimen.
I do it as a kind of beauty regimen.
A kind of beauty regimen.
That's true.
Maybe it's a kind of beauty regimen.
But it's not a wrong way to use perfume.
That's what it's all about, isn't it?
Perfume was created by people in the past to hide smells, right?
Yes, that's right.
That's one theory.
There is a theory.
Yassun is just to wash it off.
Yassun washes where he washes.
He washes where he washes.
You don't wash where you don't wash where you don't wash
He doesn't wash the places he doesn't wash.
I heard it's not good to wash your body too much.Too much body washing is bad, apparently.
The Tamori method.
I hear you use the right amount of oil.
That kind of thing.
Heh.
Yeah.
Yum, it's delicious.
Tell me your favorite smell.
What's your favorite smell? What's my favorite smell? Do you have a favorite smell?
Jasmine.
Jasmine... it's a nice smell, that's for sure.
I buy so much perfume that smells like jasmine.
You know what I mean? Do you use it?
I really like the smell of jasmine in Lior's perfume.
It's delicious.
It smells so good.
I love it. I also really like the smell of the person wearing it.
I hear that.
Do you know what a fragrance of fragrant osmanthus is?
I love the smell of fragrant fragrant rhinoceros. I know. I like the smell after it rains.
It's not perfume or anything, but after it rains, there's a unique smell, you know?
I like that smell.
I go for a walk in the middle of the night after it rains just to get that smell.
It's kind of nice, isn't it?
It smells so good after it rains.
I love the smell of bedding after it's been dried out in the sun.
The other day, there was a make-up artist who has a pet in the sun.
I learned from the internet that they dry futons in the sun.
She said it smells like dust mites.
I had learned that it's the smell of dead mites.
When he told me that my pet smelled like that.
I told her that it was the smell of dead mites.
Then I looked it up, and it turns out that it's not the smell of dead mites, but the smell of washing detergent made by exposure to the sun.
It's the chemical reaction of laundry detergent and other chemicals produced by exposure to the sun.
Wow.
Actually, no.
That's a big relief.
When I smelled the mites like that, I thought they smelled good.
I hated it when I found out.
I thought I'd lived my whole life thinking I smelled like dust mites.
But then I checked again.
Wow.
You're really smart.
I looked it up recently.
We've been talking about smells all day.
Let's go get another one.
No, I'm done. I'm going to eat.
Let's go next time.
What's the next question?
Good for you.
Momopei.
I think we're done with the survey.
That's for sure.
I'll take it.
Which one will it be?
Five, four, three, two, one. Thank you very much.
I don't know which one I'm going to get, but you can't choose 7.
Are there any more 7s? Are there any more 7s?
Then we'll go to 5... 5...
There's something you've been wanting to tell me for a while now.
I have an announcement! I've been wanting to tell you!
I like saunas.
Yes, and you know...
I often go to sauna when I go on an expedition.
So all kinds of people can use them. It's totally fine, but the other day, at a benefit...
I saw that girl with the front teeth in the sauna!
That's a big deal! She said she saw him.
I couldn't think of anything to say to her.
What did you say?
What? Naked love!
You suck at it!
I saw it! I saw it! You wanna see it, right? You wanna see it, right? And he said yes.
But if I saw it, that means I saw it, too, so that means I saw it, too.
I wonder if she's watching?
I don't know if she's close to you.
No, it's not a save if it's the same sex!
It's not a save, no matter what you think.
She's standing up.
We're both looking at each other.
But you're not looking at her, are you?
I didn't notice.
If that's the case, if you were the same sex, I wish you would've talked to her right then.
Then, if I'm still of that gender, I wish you would've talked to me at that moment.
The other day...
You know what? The hotel in front of Tamako had a big bath.
And they only had showers.
But I was tired from the show, and I wanted to take a bath and jump in the tub.
So we said, "Let's not do it at night, just in case we both decide to go.
We woke up in the morning and decided to go.
I passed Maya, and she said, "Good morning.
And then there was another one.
I went in after that... in the morning... again.
There was another sister.
And that one...
She probably noticed. Mirei? She talked to me.
I was like, "Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I was like, "Wait, wait, wait, wait," and it was morning and I was kind of spaced out.
I was like, "Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.I'm like, "Wait, what do I do?
It's all falling apart.
How did you feel? How did it feel?
You should get a little more nasally.
You're right.
I'd rather you tell me later like you did, Maya.
You're that way, aren't you?
I thought food and clothing were fine.
I don't know what it was, but... it was like I suddenly became an idol.
I said thank you.
I said thank you the way I said it yesterday.
I felt really good.
Seriously.
I was like, "I'm in it too.
It's true, we're all in this together.
But I'd like to wait.
If you met him in private...
Seriously, super.
I could understand if we met on a non-show day or something.
But if you met me yesterday on the sparkling stage...
In my costume.
Standing right in front of me.
I don't know...
What? I was like, "What?
The gap between the next person and the first was just too big.
You're right.
I was like...
I don't like either one of them.
Which one do you like better? I'm getting paranoid.
I think I'd be surprised if she went.
But I've been staring at his face for so long, I'm not sure he'd go for you, either.
That's right... when you meet someone like this...
You'd rather look at his face than his body.
Huh? Huh?
It's kind of funny.
He says it's a world where men can't exist.
But that's exactly what men are.
Charismatic teachers.
Or the principal.
That's a little awkward, too.
You're so proud of yourself for not tweeting about it.
That's because you're too net-literate.
I don't think that's a good idea.
That's the worst thing you can do.
That's not a good idea.
Thank you.
It's our little secret.
It really is.
We both know who saw it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That was really funny.
I laughed so hard.
Here we are.
Yeah, it was.
It's hard to find that moment, isn't it?
It's hard.
What do you do?
We're both fans of each other.
But you say...
You can't just say you don't know and pretend you don't know.
There are moments when you just can't.
What's the plan? Sign.
When he does this...
I thought we were family.
We'd both be like, "Oh, I like your bathtub.
But you know what?
Can I say something?
It's kind of fuzzy, but...
I'm not sure... but maybe we can make some Ebichu sound goods...
Maybe we can make a sound product of EBITCHU.
I don't know.
But if that's the case, if we can do it...
That's true, if we could...
It would be the easiest thing to understand.
If you like Ebichu, I'm sure you'll get it.
I'm sure they'll get it.
That's true.
That would be a good pattern.
It's very obvious that he's a family member, isn't it?
Let's do it a little later.
But you can do it.
There are patterns that don't use that.
It would be nice if we did.
But it's definitely recognizable from a distance.
It's a good thing.
I'm going to use it.
You will?
That, too.
Mire-chan wants one, but...
We haven't been going to the sauna together lately.
She's too stylish.
She'd know.
"I want you, Mire!
I want Mire no matter where I am.
So...
I don't like it.No, I don't.
And, uh... you know, I met the staff once.
Oh, yeah?
I met the author.
Oh, you met the author?
Isn't that awkward, too?
You know, with someone you work with.
We're going to have a naked date.
I mean...
We used to work together.
Sumi and Uchi.
You took a bath with Sumi, right?
Right.
The five of us.
We did.
At the Curry Bar.
That time, too.
It was a little awkward.
I'm not awkward anymore.
After the show.
We showered.
I don't want to sound like a sexual harasser, but...
I had to put my costume away.
I was handing it to you.
You're showing me your tits.
Please.
I was saying, "Please.
It was a little embarrassing for me to see.
I felt so bad.
Oh, you mean that's how you feel... about your fans.
That's what you mean.
I see.
That's what I meant.
I mean, it's okay if they know each other, but I don't think it's okay if they know each other.
I mean, I know some of the members. I see.
That's true.
That's what happened.
I don't know, for both of us, maybe we should just not say anything and take it to our graves.
Or we can keep it between us... or we can give some kind of sign.
I got a comment earlier that we should just pose like crazy, but if we did that, wouldn't it be dangerous?
If she does this because we're crossing paths, it's like she likes me.
It's kind of funny, but I probably wouldn't want to go out because it would be awkward if I ran into you.
I might not be able to resist the urge to get ready in that moment.
I've seen it once, I'm in a sauna right now, and I want to be in it right now.
I'd love to see you in a sauna.
I'm going to treasure my time.
I'm looking forward to meeting you in the sauna. One more thing.
One more word? How many members would you like for the last one?
I don't mind people seeing my beauty, because it's my world.
I know, I know. A well-dressed face is just too ugly.
I wish Kimoto-san would take me to a sauna.
I know a great sauna.
Five, four, three, two, one.
And... there you have it.
Here it is. Number six.
Saunata, no.
That's part two.
That's right. This way.
This is Hoshina-san.
Recently, I've been meeting some of the staff in private.
I've been running into staff members in private lately.
Outside of the sauna. - Today...
I'm meeting the boss at the hospital.
I'm going to meet her at the hospital.
I thought I've seen him before, and then he just appeared in front of me.
What's that?
What's that? What's that?
More and more.
And I only said hello once.
I was actually looking at it again.
Oh, yeah.
We met twice at the hospital.
We both go there regularly.
I go regularly, too, like once a week.
We're on the same cycle.
So we'll see each other again.
I think we go on the same days, but at different times of the day.
But only one of us has an aura of another dimension.
Right?
You know why I said I didn't want to go with you?
I definitely want Mirei's.
What?
I'm just so excited.
I understand.
I often look at your private life.
I see her when I'm in town.
I see Mirei on the street.
But I don't like the way you just talked to her.
What do you mean you don't like it?
Because you stand out.
You stand out.
Is that so?
You're wearing horror lace.
Mirei, we don't do saunas at the hospital.
Put it on.
I'm not naked, Mirei.
I'm wearing it. Don't worry.
I'm wearing it.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes.Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, well, something.
So the other day...
I go to Akashin really often.
Oh, often.
I like spicy food.
I really like spicy food.
I have a friend from junior high school and high school who I hang out with all the time.
And they call me "Pekay" after "Pé" of Mirepen.
Heh...
It's called Pekay.
So, you're expanding to MillePens?
They call me Pécé Company.
Pecai Company.
It's a dinner party for Pecompany's joint meeting.
We always say, "Let's have a meeting, let's have a meeting, let's have a meeting.
We go out to eat together.
And it just happened to be on AMETALK.
a restaurant where you can have lunch by yourself.
Akanshin came up.
They came up with "Akanspicy".
He said, "Oh no!
It's always been popular, but now it's going to be even more popular.
We had to go there.
We're saving up points for the red hot sauce.
We all scratch it off every day.
That's why we've been so hardcore about it.
We said, "This is a bad idea.
We'll make plans for next week.
And the other day we finished shooting early.
So we said, "Let's all go together then.
It just so happened that everyone was available.
I thought it would be fun to go with everyone.
I thought it would be fun.
And then the elevator opened.
Hmm? There was a guy with a T-shirt that said "Shrimp in the Shrimp" on it.
What? A fan?
That was Nassie.
Nassie, our manager-girl manager.
She was wearing a long T-shirt that day at the shoot.
She was wearing the long T-shirt in the middle of the shrimp.
And there was Mu-chan next to her.
Hmm? It was like we were the same two people who went together just a while ago.
I was so surprised.
What? What? Like...
I thought maybe they just came for a quick bite to eat.
I went there with, like, five people.
I was like, "If you go to Aka, it's not safe for you.
They came right out of Aka.
You had reservations.
I had a reservation, but it wasn't crowded.
But it wasn't crowded enough to make a reservation.
You didn't have any of that media power.
It wasn't crowded.
But then I remembered.
It's summer, right?
And then, poof!
There was our table
And on the other side of the table
And on the other side of the table, there was a table for the princesses.
And it was like a manager's girls' night out.
It was like a manager's girls' night out.
And there were more and more and more and more.
And more and more and more.
I was on line with Uchi and others all the time.
Then Uchi, who I was on line with, came popping in.
Uchi knows my friends and stuff.
He said, "It's been a long time, Somakacchan.
Mirei is always so nice to me.
She was like a mother to me.
And we were just going through the motions.
And the singer was excited.
But the girl manager...
We all got along better than I thought we would.
Yeah.
They're all different ages.
I wondered what it was like.
I thought it would be unusual to have a women's manager's group.
Everyone seems to be having a lot of fun.
That's great.
If you want, you can stay longer than us.
She was still going on about it.
I didn't mean to eat too fast.
It was a real girls' night out.
So, I'm just checking in on Instagram and stuff.
I always send it to the line.
That, too.
The manager's there.
So just wave your phone at her from a distance.
Look! Look!
Look at the line! Look at the line!
And write, "Yes, sir.
I didn't think that was possible.
That's great. That's possible.
I didn't know that was possible.
That's awkward.
Because more than half the people in the restaurant
I knew.
It's awkward.
Awkward.It's awkward.
I've had that happen.
It's homey.
I'm sure.
No doubt about it.
They look like they're having so much fun.
They look like they're having a lot of fun.
The world is a small place.
It's so small.
The ending?
What's that? What's this?
I couldn't do the chat thing.
GDP.
It's not GDP.
GPT
I couldn't get the chat GPT to work.
I'll do it next time.
Please don't say it halfway.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We'll see you next time.
Next time, we'll bring you the Shrimp in the Shrimp GPT!
This is going to be a great and absolutely fun project!
I have no doubt about it, so please look forward to it!
Thank you very much.
Okay, so...
We also did taco bread.
Yes, it was delicious!
It was delicious.
To be honest, I don't even remember what we talked about today.
Takoyaki was so good!
They were really good!
But when I was talking with Maya.
I really don't remember what we're talking about.
I don't remember.
And if you want, you know...
As you said in your comment.
When we're talking and talking together...
The conversation got faster and faster.
It was so fast that the first morning jump went off.
That was the fastest backwards speed I've ever heard.
I hope you all enjoyed the show.
Now I'd like to announce the ranking.
Fifth place, thank you Riku!
4th place, thank you, Machika for your nervousness!
Third place, thank you, Ooya-san!
2nd place, Thank you Shinato-san!
1st, Thank you, Tamamin!
The top rankers are
That's what it is, isn't it?
You don't change your clothes by Katakuna's will, do you?
In the shrimp
Only Tamamin-san
Only Tamamin-san.
You're particular, aren't you?
You're very particular, aren't you, all of you?
You're super lurkers.
Super roomer.
That's nice.
I hope someday I can get her to change out of this.
I'm sure if I asked you to change right away, you'd change.
That's for sure.
I don't think so.
I have an announcement to make.
I have an announcement.
This is Chiritsu Ebi Chugakko Spring Tour 2023.
100% EBISM is underway!
June 24th at Miyagi Electron Hall
And on July 1st at Ibaraki-za Hirosawa City Hall
There is still time to get tickets for these shows.
We are looking forward to seeing you there!
The other shows are sold out
Thankfully, the other shows are sold out.
So please come and see us for the two performances.
We hope you can come and see us!
Next time, we will be in Osaka!
If you have tickets
We'll be waiting for you.
Yes, and...
Yes, and the summer family production of EBICHU!
The family production held
Lake Yamanaka 2023 will be
August 5 and 6
Yamanakako Koryu Plaza
Kirara Theater
will be held at Hibiki
This is an annual event for Fami-en
This year, AMIUM will join us!
This will be our first Fami performance in December.
This year, too, at the Paku Paku Utamura
We are planning a project for Choo Ching.
We're going to make a choo-chin with your name on it, or rather
You can decorate the choo-chin with your name
You can decorate it with your name or any letters you like.
We are looking forward to your visit.
We are also thinking of doing a collaboration menu.
We are thinking about it.
We are working on it.
We are also planning to produce some very cute goods.
Animals.
Not animals.This is not an animal.
This one is an animal.
This one is made to look like an animal.
We have some goodies on the way.
Please look forward to it!
Please.
And, you know...
Yas.
Sack
Cocona
Emma
And also
and Kobayashi
Ladies and gentlemen
We will have a birthday party as well.
I hope you will check them out as well
I would be happy if you could celebrate with us.
So the five of us are all together at this time of the year?
In a manner of speaking
I know it's a little bit off.
Two in June and two in August.
But it's a little bit different.
But you know, it's going on and on and on and on.
We have a rush of birthdays coming up.
Birthdays are coming soon.
Birthdays are coming soon!
And we're missing out on birthday presents, too.
You say we didn't get you a birthday present.
That's right.
I think it should be for two years.
Once every two years.
I thought it'd be nice.
We'll make some money. It's a small number.
Maybe once every two years.
One drop. You can have one drop.
It's okay, isn't it?
No, I can't.
Sorry.
Kaho, it's the day after tomorrow.
It's your birthday, right?
That's right.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Yes, so...
Shrimp in the Showroom of Fun and Funny
As soon as we decide on the next showroom
I will let you know as soon as it is decided.
Any chance for a review meeting?
No, no, no.
Of course not.
You talked a lot.
I don't know how to reflect on that.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Maybe.
If there's anything to be sorry for...
If you have anything to be sorry about...
And give us an item called takoyaki
And allowed this to happen.
I'm most sorry that I allowed this to happen.
Yes, you're right.
I talk a lot, don't I?
Yes, we do.
You'll have a better meeting next time.
I think we'll have a different taste next time.
I don't think your ears will be as tired.
Thanks for listening to me so much.
Thank you very much.
See you again.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.